Every single Venezuelan person that has responded to me saying they are in support of the United
States going in to get rid of Maduro has sounded like a Karen, has sounded like MAGA.
They all lead with insults.
None of them lead with an attempt to teach.
They all lead with an attempt to discredit.
All of them are vague in why they are against Maduro.
They say that he has been harming people, that he's been kidnapping people, etc.
They don't say who he's kidnapping.
They don't say who he's harming.
They don't say why.
If you ask me, who is the United States government harming and kidnapping and why, I can tell you.
And I can pretty much tell you that for the past 40 years.
And it includes Venezuelans.
What I have noticed is that whenever folks are not wanting to be specific about why they fall into a group that has had to flee or that is being repressed, oftentimes it is because they are not proud of the reason why.
And what that tells me is that you are not representative of the people that I would probably be rocking with was I in Venezuela.
Because the shady folks all speak the same way everywhere.
Everywhere.
Whether they speak the same language, they all use the same tactics.
Yep.
I think you'll find, sir, that there will come a time when black people wake up and become intellectually independent enough to think for themselves.
As other humans are intellectually independent enough to think for themselves, then the black man will think like a black man.
And he will feel for other black people.
And this new thinking and feeling will cause black people to stick together.